Drawn by a landscape as white as snow,
真っ白な景色にいま誘われて
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
I'm headed toward an unseen world.
僕は行くよ　まだ見ぬ世界へ
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
I've been traveling while lost
迷子のまま旅していた
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
Under this gray sky.
鼠色の空の下
Nezumiiro no sora no shita
Every day with new maps, stained with my many dreams.
日替わりの地図 いくつもの夢が滲んでいた
Higawari no chizu ikutsumo no yume ga nijindeita
I wonder if someday,
いつかはさ
Itsuka wa sa
Even with these tiny steps of mine,
ちっぽけな僕のこの歩幅でも
Chippoke na boku no kono hohaba demo
I'll be able to travel beyond those clouds.
あの雲の向こうまで行けるかな
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
I put on a bold front.
強がって
Tsuyogatte
End up hurting myself.
キズついた
Kizutsuita
I feel empty inside.
心透かしたように
Kokoro sukashita youni
It's started to rain,
降り出した
Furidashita
And the raindrops
雨粒たちが
Amatsubu tachi ga
Began to repeat their scattered reflections.
乱反射繰り返す
Ranhansha kurikaesu
These straight rays of light
真っ直ぐな光が
Massugu na hikari ga
Start to cross one another.
交差して
Kousa shite
And without telling anyone where they're headed,
行き先も告げぬまま
Yakusaki mo tsugenumama
Across the endless distances,
どこまでも
Doko made mo
They pass through all matter.
突き抜ける
Tsukinukeru
I burn these faint afterimages onto my eyes.
淡い残像　両目に焼きつけて
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakitsukete
Under this sky,
この空の下
Kono sora no shita
Wherever I am,
どんなとこにいても
Donna toko ni itemo
I should be able to reach
届くはずなんだ
Todoku hazu nanda
The unseen world.
まだ見ぬ世界へ
Mada minu sekai e
Resembool! We're in Resembool!
リゼンブール　リゼンブールだよっと
So what exactly are the Colonel's orders?
大佐の命令って何なんだよ
Can't you tell me already, Major?
いいかげん話してくれよ　少佐
I don't know many of the details, either.
我が輩も詳しくは聞いておらん
I was simply told to bring you along to Resembool to meet up with the others.
ただ　お主を連れてリゼンブールで合流せよと
Meet up with who?
合流って　誰と
Good day, Major Armstrong.
どうも　アームストロング少佐　と
And...
Yo, Boss.
よう　大将
Second Lieutenant Breda?!
ブレダ少尉
Brother should have arrived in Resembool a while ago...
兄さん
リゼンブールにはとっくに着いているはずなのに
...but he still hasn't called...
連絡ないね
And besides, I'm here if he needs to have his arm repaired.
そもそも　修理なら私がいるのに
There's so much we don't know,
including Second Lieutenant Ross' case...
ロス少尉の件といい
分からないことだらけだ
Which is why I'm here to explain.
だから説明に来たんだ
S-Since when?!
いっ　いつの間に
Where did you even come in from?!
っていうかどこから
The window.
窓から
I'm technically a criminal, after all.
ほら　一応犯罪者だしね
SMUGGLED INTO THE COUNTRY
AND
BROKE OUT OF JAIL
Well, you guys don't need to worry about Edward.
あっ　エドワードのことなら心配いらないよ
Right now, he's probably...
今ごろはたぶん
So hot...
熱ぃ
That damn Colonel... he didn't mention a word about us having to leave the country...
国を出るなんて聞いてねぇぞ　大佐の野郎
Mr. Han, are we almost there?
ハンさん　目的地はまだですかね
We've been here for a while now.
とっくに着いてるよ
See? The Xerxes ruins.
ほら　クセルクセス遺跡だ
Whew~
I almost burned myself with my automail...
Why is the brat with you?
なんで小僧がいるのだ
For certain reasons.
ちょっと訳ありでな
Xerxes, huh...
クセルクセスか
I remember reading about it in
the tale about the Sage of the East.
「東の賢者の話」で読んだっけ
Sage of the East?
東の賢者
Yeah.
ああ
A fairy tale about the alchemist who introduced alchemy to our country.
オレたちの国に錬金術を伝えた術師のおとぎ話だよ
It's a legend about the sole survivor of the
Xerxes Kingdom, which was destroyed in one night,
一夜にして滅んだクセルクセス王国の生き残りが
and how he arrived in Amestris, just recently founded
at that time, and spread alchemy throughout the country.
建国から間もなかったころのアメストリスに流れ着いて
錬金術を広めたって伝説
我が国には　西から流れ着いたという伝説がある
In our country, there's a legend stating he arrived from the west.
Eastern alchemy as we know it today is a combination of the skills he brought us and Xing's technology.
彼が伝えた技術と　シンの技術が合わさり
今の錬丹術となったらしい
Oh, the one developed as a method of healing?
医学方面に発達したっていうあれか
That's right.
We refer to him with respect,
我々は彼のことを　尊敬を持って呼んでいる
as the "Sage of the West".
「西の賢者」と
And this is where that sage was from?
その賢者の出身がここだったと
That's what's been told.
そう伝えられている
Wow...
I wanted to see the Xerxes ruins.
クセルクセス遺跡を見ておきたかったから
Now I see why...
なるほど　それでか
But I wonder if it's truly possible for them to be destroyed in one night despite having advanced technology like this.
しっかし　こんだけの技術を持ちながら
一夜で滅ぶなんてことがあるのかね
It could just be a legend.
ただの伝説かもしれんがな
What are you doing?
何をしている　こっちだ
This way.
We're going in pretty deep, aren't we...
随分奥まで行くんだな
Edward!
エドワード君
Eastern Headquarters, where I used to be stationed, was great.
私がいた東部　あそこはいいぞ
It lacks the bustle of large cities,
and most of all, there are so many beauties.
都会の喧騒もないし
何より　美人が多い
That stupid colonel!
あのクソ大佐
ロス少尉
Second Lieutenant Ross!!!
Now, for the embrace of reunion!!!
さあ　再会の抱擁を
I'll pass!
結構です
Second Lieutenant Ross!
ロス少尉
There's no telling when we'd get caught if a dead person was walking around the country, so we had her flee.
死んだ人間が国内にいちゃ
どこでバレるか分かんねぇからよ
国外に出したんだ
So the Colonel knew all along
Second Lieutenant Ross was innocent?
じゃあ大佐は　ロス少尉が無実だと分かってて
Don't you think you're being a bit too flashy?
動きが派手すぎやしませんかね
You think so, too?
お前もそう思うか
Yes.
Hauling her down to the police station in front of a crowd...
大勢の前で連行したり
Murdering a colleague is an embarrassment to the military, and yet, to have it make headlines...
軍にとって不名誉である同僚殺しを
でかでかと新聞に載せたり
It's me.
私だ
A call from Warrant Officer Falman on a general line, sir.
ファルマン准尉から　一般回線で通信です
Put it through.
つなげ
Colonel! About the murder of Brigadier General Hughes...
大佐　ヒューズ准将殺害の件ですが
Hey Falman! Let me talk to him for a bit.
おいファルマン
ちょいと電話貸しな
Barry?!
バリー
Yo, Mr. Mustang! Did you see the paper?
よう　マスタングさん
新聞見たかい
I've got something interesting to tell you.
おもしろい話があるんだけどよ
Hey, Barney! You shouldn't use this line for private use!
やあ　バーニー
私用電話はいけないなぁ
I'll call you back from outside my office, so hang tight!
外から掛け直すから　ちょっと待っていたまえ
What? Is that true?
何　それは本当か
Yeah, the bullet the lieutenant used was the one she shot me with.
ああ　少尉の使った弾ってのはオレを撃ったときのだ
I still have the hole in my right hand.
今でも撃たれた穴が右手に残ってるぜ
I think we can set something up...
仕掛けてみるか
Huh?
Barry, don't you miss going on rampages?
バリー　久々に暴れてみたくはないか
ほう　へへへっ　了解
Roger. I won't kill.
人は殺さねぇよ
The second passage to the warehouse district, right?
倉庫街の２番通路だな
Breda, go find these ingredients right away.
ブレダ　大至急これを集めろ
Pork bones and meat, carbon, ammonia.
「豚の骨と肉　炭素　アンモニア」
What's all this for?
なんですか
I'm going to whip up a burnt corpse.
焼死体を一つでっちあげる
H-Human transmutation?!
じっ　人体錬成
Don't be stupid.
バカ言うな
It's going to be something that resembles a burnt corpse.
あくまで焼死体のようなものだ
But if the medical examiner looks closely...
そんなもん　検視官に見られたら
I'm going to burn it up so badly they won't even be able to have it appraised.
鑑定などできないくらい消し炭にする
But what will you do if they decide to check the treatment marks on her teeth?
歯の治療痕を照合されたらどうするんですか
It's all under control.
手は打った
Will you be able to do it?
できるんですか
I'm no expert, but I do know enough to make it happen.
専門ではないが　それなりに知識は持っている
I'm also good at transmuting burnt corpses.
焼死体をつくるのは得意だ
Hurry!
急げ
You're Maria Ross, right?
マリア·ロスだな
It's a dummy.
ダミーだ
You're going to die here tonight.
君は今夜　ここで死ぬ
Don't just sit there.
ぼさっとするな
Oww...
痛っ
しぃ
Yo, Fullmetal.
やあ　鋼の
What's the meaning of this, Colonel?!
どういうことだ　大佐
Huh? Was that the fullmetal boss?
ありゃ　鋼の大将
That's not good... this was unexpected.
まいったなぁ　予定外だ
Edward...
エドワード君
Well, the Colonel will take care of it.
まあ　大佐がなんとかしてくれるだろ
Let's go.
行くぞ
Roger.
はい
While Barry was helping Ms. Ross break out of jail,
he made a deal with the Young Master.
ロス殿を脱獄させた際
若とバリーが取り引きをしておってな
And the Young Master commanded me to escort her to the east.
わしが若より受けた命令は
この女を東へ運ぶこと
And we promised him we'd meet here to set Second Lieutenant Ross free.
ここで合流する約束をして
ロス少尉を逃がしたってわけだ
I see.
なるほど
I still don't like it...
気に入らねぇな
It means the bastard colonel pulled a fast one on us, right?
大佐の野郎に一杯食わされたってことだろ
It's more convincing to actually have you see her than to explain it in words, right?
口で説明するより
ロス少尉と会わせた方が納得しやすいだろ
I know, I know.
分かってる分かってる
The Colonel is totally right this time.
今回は大佐の言うとおりだよ
Speaking of the Colonel...
その大佐だがな
I also recall him saying, "Having a pissed-off brat around the place would just be a total nuisance to the mission!"
頭に血が上ったヤツにうろうろされては
作戦の邪魔になる　とも言ってたっけ
That damned colonel!!!
あのクソ大佐
What is this mission you speak of?
作戦とは
Is there something else to do aside from rescuing Second Lieutenant Ross?
ロス少尉の救出以外にも何かあるのか
Yes.
ええ
We decided to fish out the mastermind hiding within the military.
軍に巣くっている黒幕を釣り上げてやろうと思いましてね
Next time I see him...
今度会ったら
Fish out?
釣り上げる
Barry, who knows the secret behind
Research Laboratory 5, went out and made a mess.
第五研究所の秘密を握るバリーが
あれだけ派手に暴れたんだ
They'll definitely come to shut him up for good.
必ず口封じにやってくるさ
So that's how it was.
そんなことになってたんだ
So the only reason they took Ed was because he'd be a nuisance?
もしかして
エドが連れていかれたのって
ただの厄介払い
ふふっそうだね
I guess you could say that.
And I lent them a hand in exchange for Barry telling me the secret to his body.
で
オレはバリーってヤツの体の秘密を教えてもらう代わりに
手を貸したってわけ
But it turns out...
ところがさ
The scientist who turned me into this is long dead, so I don't really know.
オレをこんな体にした研究者はもう死んじまってるから
よく分かんねぇんだよ
What?! That's not fair!
ええ　そりゃないでしょ
Oh yeah, that Alphonse guy is kind of in the same boat as me, so why don't you try asking him?
そうだ
あのアルフォンスってヤツも似たような体だから
あいつから聞いてくれや
So I decided to come to you instead.
ってことで　君から聞くことにしたよ
It's a promise, so I'm counting on you!
約束だから　よろしくね
えっと　その約束って僕無関係なんだけど
Umm... I really don't have anything to do with that promise...
I really have nothing to do with this, do I...
ほんと無関係よね　私
Philosopher's stones... Homunculus...
賢者の石とか　人造人間とか
I wonder why I was dragged into all this.
なんで巻き込まれちゃったんだろう
Now we have quite a bit of information.
これでかなりの情報が出そろった
If we discover the truth behind the murder of the Brigadier General, the situation will change, too.
准将殺しの真相が分かれば　状況も変わるさ
We'll definitely prove you were falsely accused.
お主の冤罪は　我々が晴らしてみせる
Lieute- Brigadier General Hughes...
ヒューズ中　准将
本当に　死んじまったんだな
He's really gone, isn't he...
What do you plan to do now?
これから　どうするつもりだ
Move forward on the path you're content with.
自分たちが納得する方法で　前へ進みなさい
We have someone who's willing to collaborate with us, even though we committed taboo...
禁忌を犯したオレたちに　協力してくれる人がいる
We also have someone who'll scold and support us...
怒ってくれる人　支えてくれる人がいる
I have a younger brother who I made a promise with... to return to our bodies...
元の体に戻ろうと約束した　弟がいる
I also don't have anywhere to return...
そして　後戻りはできない
With that said, I have no choice but to move forward...
だったら　前に進むしかないじゃないか
In a way that won't cause a single death of anyone important to me.
誰一人失わない方法で
If it seems someone is going to be victimized, I'll protect them.
もし誰かが犠牲になりそうになったら　オレが守る
It may be difficult.
難しいことかもしれない
It's hard enough keeping my own head, but protecting others, too...
自分の身一つで精一杯なのに
他人まで守ろうだなんて　傲慢かもしれない
It may be arrogant of me,
but this is the only thing I can think of,
でも　今のオレにはこれしか思いつかない
so I'm going to move forward.
だから進むよ　前に
Second Lieutenant Ross, what do you plan to do now?
ロス少尉　お主はこれからどうする
I plan to go to the country of Xing.
はい　シンの国へ行こうと思います
Should I at least let your parents know?
両親にだけでも知らせておくか
No.
いえ
If it happens that information about me being alive is leaked from my parents, it'd be irreparable.
万が一私が生きていることが　両親の口から漏れれば
取り返しのつかないことになります
I see.
そうか
Major Armstrong. Second Lieutenant Breda.
アームストロング少佐
ブレダ少尉
Hm?
Please pass a message to Colonel Mustang for me.
マスタング大佐にお伝えください
"I greatly appreciate you saving me."
救ってくださったことに　感謝しますと
Ask him to order me back in the case of emergency.
そして　有事の際には呼び戻してください
I will gladly risk my life to assist him if that ever happens!
そのときは　命を懸けて働かせていただきますと
I will.
Stay well, Edward.
元気でね　エドワード君
I never got you back for that slap.
ビンタの借り　返せなかった
Maybe next time.
また今度ね
Yeah. Maybe next time.
ああ　また今度
You have good friends.
よい仲間を持ったな
Mr. Fu, what is Xing like?
フーさん　シンはどんな国ですか
It's a pleasant country, with great food and nice people.
人も食べ物も豊かで
懐の深いよい国だ
There's no need to worry.
安心するがよい
So I can expect a paradise after crossing this desert, right?
この砂漠を越えたら　楽園があると思っていいんですね
うむ　ただし
You sure can.
However, crossing this desert is a cruel task in itself.
この砂漠越えがなかなか過酷でな
Careful.
気をつけろよ
You should conserve your fluids.
今からあまり水分を浪費するな
I'll drop by your store tomorrow.
明日あたり　店に寄るよ
What do you want as your gift, Elizabeth?
お土産は何がいい　エリザベス
あっと　ごめんなさいロイさん
Pardon me, Roy.
Kate, we have customers.
ケイト　お客さんが来たわ
Could you go get Jacquelyn?
ジャクリーンを呼んでくれる
Jacquelyn, we have customers.
ジャクリーン　客が来ましたよ
Roger.
了解
Whoa!
Barry!
バリー
Calm down, Falman.
落ち着けよ　ファルマン
You can't kill this one!
こいつは殺しちゃダメだぜ
This smell of cigarettes...
このタバコのにおい
Second Lieutenant Havoc?!
ハボック少尉
Hey! What do you think I'm disguised for?!
お前な　なんのために覆面してると思ってんだ
This is why I can't stand guys who aren't used to battles!
これだから現場慣れしてねぇヤツはよ
I-I'm sorry, sir!
すっ　すみません
You were only "dragged in".
お前は巻き込まれただけってことになってる
So don't attack him.
手は出すなよ
Someone from the army could be watching us at any moment.
どこで軍の連中が見張ってるか分からねぇんだ
You...
お前
We're heading outside!
外に出るぞ
But there may be enemies outside!
しかし　外には敵がいるかもしれませんよ
We don't have to worry about that.
外は大丈夫だ
Shit!
しまった
Second Lieutenant!
少尉
Don't worry, we have the hawkeye on our side.
心配すんな
オレたちには鷹の目が付いている
I just heard a loud noise. Is something wrong?
大きな音がしたが　どうした
Nothing at all.
大丈夫よ
The customer played a prank on Jacquelyn, so I hit him a little.
お客さんがジャクリーンにいたずらしたから
少したたいてやっただけ
Oh my.
おやおや
You're harsh, Elizabeth.
手厳しいねエリザベス
All right, don't move.
よし　動くなよ
We have a lot to ask you... er...
いろいろと聞きたいことがって
Does he understand what we're saying?
こいつ言葉通じるのか
You've gotta be kidding me...
おい　うそだろ
This is...
こいつは
That's my body!!!
これはオレの体だ
What?! How could this be?!
何っ　どういうことだ
They threw in some kind of experimental animal or a soul inside my body!
ヤツらオレの体に
実験動物か何かの魂ほうり込みやがった
And now, he's here to get his soul back!
肉体が魂よこせってやってきたんだよ
This brings back so many memories!
懐かしいぜぇ
I haven't seen it since I had my soul pulled out of me!
魂ひっぺがされて以来のご対面だ
A transmutation circle.
練成陣
It's similar to the one I saw in Research Laboratory 5.
第五研究所にあったのと似てるけど
A two-headed dragon... A sun...
二頭の竜　太陽
Agh, dammit! The top part's gone, so I can't tell anything!
くそっ　上の方欠けてて分かんねぇや
Need something from me?
なんか用かい
If it's money, I don't-
言っとくけど金は
An Ishbalan?
イシュヴァール人か
Young lad, would you become a hostage in order for us to get our holy land back from the army?
少年よ　国軍から我らの聖地を取り戻すため
人質になってはくれんか
There's no way the army would give in for one kid like me.
軍がこんなガキ１人のために　動くわきゃねぇだろ
The civil war began with the death of a child, as well.
あの内乱も　引き金は１人の子供の死だった
We don't know what could be
the beginning of a change in history.
何が歴史を変えるきっかけになるか　分からんのだよ
Cut it out; this is disgraceful.
やめんか見苦しい
Lady Shan!
シャン様
You idiots...
バカ者が
Are you trying to bring shame to the Ishbalan name?
イシュヴァラの名を辱める気か
Could you let that man go?
He won't try to harm you anymore.
その人を放してあげて　もう襲ったりしないから
Why did you save me?
なんで助けた
Don't you all hate Amestrians?
あんたらはアメストリス人を憎んでるはずだろ
I know that not all Amestrians are evil.
すべてのアメストリス人が
悪でないことを知っておるからじゃ
Both Lady Shan and I were saved by Amestrian doctors when we were badly injured during the civil war.
シャン様も僕も　内乱で大ケガをしたときに
アメストリス人のお医者さんに助けてもらったんだ
In all honesty, we despise your kind, but I wouldn't be here today if it weren't for that couple.
正直　君たちが憎いけど
僕が生きているのも
あのお医者さん夫婦のお陰なんだ
Couple?
夫婦
Could you be talking about the Rockbells?!
まさか　ロックベルって名前じゃ
You know Doctor Rockbell?
君　ロックベル先生の知り合いなの
Y-Yeah...
The doctor saved so many of us Ishbalans.
先生は
僕たちイシュヴァールの民を何人も救ってくれたんだ
I see...
そうか
So Uncle and Aunt Rockbell...
ロックベルのおじさんとおばさんが
They stayed with us, despite the war getting worse and worse.
戦いがひどくなるなか
我らとともにいてくれた
How were their last moments?
どんな最期だった
They were killed by an Ishbalan...
夫妻は　助けた患者に
イシュヴァールの者に殺された
...an Ishbalan patient they saved.
No way...
そんな
We're so sorry...
すまない
We couldn't stop him.
わしらはあれを止められなかった
Who was it?!
どこのどいつだ
I couldn't see his face.
顔は分からなかった
But he was an Ishbalan with a tattoo on his right arm.
右腕に入れ墨のあるイシュヴァールの武僧だ
When you get the chance, please convey our feelings to their gravestones.
機会があったら
ロックベル夫妻の墓前に報告をしておいておくれ
Both our gratitude... and our apologies...
感謝と　謝罪を
This is just grand!
こいつはいいや
This is like the once-in-a-lifetime chance for me to cut up my own body as much as I want!
てめぇの肉体を思う存分ぶった斬れる機会なんて
なかなかねぇぜ
You told me earlier not to kill him!
お前　さっきは殺すなって言ってただろうが
To hell with this mission!
作戦なんてもうクソ食らえだ
My soul keeps shaking... It wants to cut him up!
魂がざわつくんだよ　斬っちまいてぇってな
You can't do that.
ダメだ
Besides, wouldn't the normal approach to this be wishing to go back inside your old body?
だいたい
元の体に戻りたいって思うのが普通じゃないのか
That body won't last much longer.
あの体　もうもたねぇよ
Oh, so it's rotten...
なんだ　腐ってるのか
I can't stand it anymore!!!
だあ　もう我慢できねぇ
I'm going to cut him up!
斬るぜ
I get to decide what to do with my own body!
オレの体をどうしようがオレの勝手だ
I said, no!
ダメだっつってんだろうが
What's wrong?
どうした
I wonder if it's a fight?
ケンカかしら
Seems like there's some trouble between her and the customer.
お客さんとトラブルみたい
Oops, I'm going to have to call you back.
いけない　電話はまたにするわ
I've got a customer, too.
こっちもお客が来てしまった
Let it all out, Let it all out
I don't have to act tough, right?
強がらなくていいんだね
Tsuyogaranakute iindane
The scribbling someone made...
誰かが描いてった
Dareka ga kaitetta
On the wall, of a flower is swaying.
壁の落書きの花が　揺れる
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
No one knows their true selves.
自分らしさなんて, 誰もわからないよ
Jibunrashisa nante dermo wakaranaiyo
Even though we both lose and gain
長い長い道の途中で
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu de
By embarking on this long, long path,
失くしたり, 拾ったり,
Nakushitari hirottari
And though there may be days loneliness strikes and makes us weep...
急に寂しくなって, 泣いちゃう日もあるけど
Kyuu ni samishikunatte naichau hi mo arukedo
Let's transform our tears and pains to stars.
涙も　痛みも　星に変えよう
Namida mo itami mo hoshi ni kaeyou
Let's light a candle to illuminate our tomorrow.
明日を照らす　灯りをともそう
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
And we'll hold our small hands over the fire to create stardust,
小さな手かざして　ふたりで作ろう
Chiisana te kazashite futari de tsukurou
And an eternity that shines so brilliantly.
星屑を　強く光る永遠を探そう
Hoshikuzu wo tsuyoku hikaru eien wo
Farewells may be unavoidable,
さよなら　いつかは来るかもしれない
Sayonara itsuka wa kurukamoshirenai
Yet the seasons continue to change obliviously.
季節はそれでも巡り巡ってく
Kisetsu wa soredemo meguri megutteku
Even if I lose myself, I'll continue to walk...
小さく迷っても　歩いてく
Chiisaku mayottemo aruiteku
Walk by your side.
君と歩いてく
Kimi to aruiteku
That's the only thing I'd like to never change.
それだけは変わらないでいようね
Sore dake wa kawaranaideiyoune
日本語字幕仕上げ：FAYFAY
その女は強く誇り高き人
She's a strong, proud woman.
仲間より慕われる美しき人
A beautiful woman, loved by her comrades.
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
だが　敵を射ぬく武器は力を失い
But her weapon which shoots down enemies has lost its power, and her flame of life fleetingly went out.
命の火は儚く消えた
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
第十九話　死なざる者の死
Episode 19, Death of the Undying.
苦悩に歪む　それは記憶のなせる業
She becomes anguished.
Her memories bring about her suffering.